(Amy:)How about the theme song
to the television show Diff'rent Strokes?
(Amy:)Now the world don't move to the
(Sheldon:)No.
(Amy:)Well, that's every song I know.
What's up?
(Sheldon:)You're good friends with Penny, right?
(Amy:)Best friends, besties.
BFFs, peas-in-a-pod...
(Amy:)...sisters who would share
traveling pants. Go on.
(Sheldon:)I was hoping she might listen to you...
(Sheldon:)...about the dangers
of owning unhygienic furniture.
(Amy:)For general educational purposes...
(Amy:)...or has she acquired a bar stool
dipped in cholera?
(Sheldon:)Cholera is water-borne.
You're mocking me.
(Priya:)Yes, I am.
(Sheldon:)Penny has dragged a chair in off
the street whose unknown provenance...
...jeopardizes the heaIth and weIfare
of every resident in our building.
(Amy:)Just because you have a focus on
cleanliness bordering on the psychotic...
(Amy:)...doesn't mean I have to participate.
(Sheldon:)All right. Name your price.